# Anthony Hien Vu

Full-Stack Web Developer

### Contact

**Address** 

Wentworthville, NSW, 2145

**Phone** 

045-266-8725

E-mail

avu120@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/anthony-hien-vu

**WWW** 

https://avu120.github.ic /portfolio

**WWW** 

https://github.com/AVu120

## **Skills**

React

Excellent

Redux

Excellent

CSS/Modules/SASS/CSS-in-JS/CSS-in-HTML

Excellent

React Testing

Excellent

Node/Express

Full-stack web developer with a strong preference for the frontend. I also have experience in QA and DevOps as well (I have 2 AWS associate certifications). Where ever I work, I'm always striving to upskill everyone in my team and learn from them too. Mentoring others and working as a cohesive team is very important to me.

## **Work History**

2021-03 -2021-09

## Full Stack Web Developer

OOh!media, Sydney, NSW

- Built new features into internal React & Redux applications.
- Built evergreen internal UI design system using Storybook.js. It is currently used by multiple stakeholders (e.g. designers, developers, product owners/managers, etc.) to standardize UI/UX across different web applications.
- Built new features in Node Express.js/GraphQL servers.
- Built new features in python API servers.
- Made configuration changes in AWS services like SQS, Lambda and EC2.
- Made configuration changes to Concourse CICD pipelines.

2018-08 -2021-02

## Full Stack Web Developer

Telstra, Sydney, NSW

- Performed full-stack development of a Telstra enterprise web application with thousands of internal users utilizing the MERN (MongoDB, Express, React, Node) stack with redux. The primary feature of this application is a catalogue of charts displaying data from various sources. I built new features into this application every day. Some examples include allowing the users to query databases from within the application, automatically schedule user-written scripts against databases, set up monitoring & alarms, and many more. The application uses a microservices architecture and is deployed on AWS.
- Go to https://avu120.github.io/portfolio/#portfolio then click on the Telstra logo to see an overview of

Good **Building REST APIs Building GraphQL APIs** Good **SQL** Databases Very Good NoSQL Databases Very Good Storybook (UI Design Very Good Figma (Design/Wireframe Languages Excellent Excellent Python Very Good

Java

most of my work at Telstra.

- Troubleshooted operational issues in AWS core services such as CloudWatch, EC2, ECR and DocumentDB.
- Containerized many applications using Docker.
- Configured NGINX reverse-proxies to forward requests to various servers/micro-services-in-dockercontainers.
- Wrote unit tests using Jest.js, Enzyme.js and React Testing Library.
- Wrote integration tests using ROBOT test framework.
- Set up CICD pipelines using Atlassian's Bamboo platform.
- Documented many APIs using Swagger/OpenAPI specification.
- Automated deployment of network configuration and virtual network devices using python scripts and ansible playbooks.

2017-02 -2018-05

#### **IT Consultant**

KPMG, Sydney, NSW

- Implemented & configured Microsoft Dynamics 365
  ERP (Enterprise Resource Planning) software for large multinational clients.
- Performed IT risk testing (audit).

## **Education**

2013-02 -2016-11

## **Bachelor of Science: Engineering**

Sydney University - Sydney, NSW

## **Certifications**

2021-03 AWS Certified Developer - Associate

2021-07 AWS Certified Solutions Architect - Associate

## **Interests**

Frontend & Backend System Architecture

C++

Good

Responsive Design (& design in general)

DevOps/Cloud/Serverless

Mentoring

Leadership

Sustainability

Machine-Learning/Al

## **Hobbies**

- Ice Skating
- Cricket
- Hiking
- Running
- Reading
- Tech Meetups